This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy raided Navy HQ to rescue his brother Ace from execution,
only to see him killed before his eyes.
Although he escaped to Amazon Lily,
he found himself consumed with despair.
I couldn't save my crew!
Or my brother!
Boy, you can't see a thing!
You're blind!
There is yet joy beyond your sorrows!
What's gone may be gone,
but you still have something left in this world to treasure!
Don't you?!
My crew!
I still have my crew!
I wish they were here right now!
I miss them!
I miss my crew!
Straw Hat's in shock!
The bad news has reached them!
Along the Grand Line,
there lies the ruins of Muggy Kingdom,
found on a place known as Gloom Island.
Yikes!
We're in trouble now!
Whoa!
They're angry!
What did that one just say?
How should I know?
Either way,
I'm not chatting it up with these guys.
There's no point...
Both Thanos.
Russian Demon Lore
Three-swords style!
Bold demon...
Bold Hulk!
Oh no! How many of these things are there?
Damn, they're smart. They're using weapons just like a human.
Three-sword style! Dragon Twister!
They reopened my wound. Is that what they were aiming for?
Dragon Twister!
Ah!
Um, you're not dead, are you?
Shut up. This is no time for you to annoy me.
What? How dare you accuse me of being annoying when I'm genuinely concerned for your safety!
Whatever, I don't care. Get eaten by the evil monkeys, why don't you?
Well, I'm screwed.
You're rude.
Ah!
What's that aura?
It's him.
There's no way.
It's Hawkeye.
Hawkeye me hawk.
Meanwhile, in Birdie Kingdom in the South Blue,
where the birds are constantly at odds with the humans.
But I don't want to be a dinner!
We catch Raccoon again for Hushpuck.
Raccoon tastes good!
I already told you, idiots!
I'm not a raccoon!
Hey, Papa, why Yummy Raccoon saying he not raccoon?
You making no sense.
Raccoon no can saying words.
I'm saying words right now, you overgrown potato!
Maybe you'd hear them if you'd shut your fat mouth!
I'm a reindeer, and I can speak like a proper human, unlike you!
Oh, and I'm a doctor, too!
That's stupid.
No way can be talking Dr. Raccoon.
Then how you know what he's saying, Papa?
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Can you get me down now?
Me helping!
Ah!
Awesome!
This is special cream for fixing burns.
We using many plants for medicine that help making better all kinds of sickness.
Is there more where this came from?
I'd love to see it!
We no more have them.
Huh?
Big tree on mountaintop, growing plants we needing to make medicine.
But last year, mean birds make nests on mountaintop, never letting us get more plant.
Almost have no good medicine left, but more and more people sick!
Friend, have big cough.
This is awful.
No hand breathing.
She could easily die from this.
No more do nothing!
We fix bird problem forever!
We're only doing what have to do!
Me not afraid!
Go helping my family!
Papa!
Son!
Me sorry.
You protect Mama now.
Hey, wait a minute!
Hey, wait a second, you guys.
Don't rush this.
As a doctor, I can't turn my back on sick patients.
Don't worry.
I'll go talk to the birds and ask them to stop picking on you, okay?
Raccoon can't talk bird.
I sure can.
All I gotta do is ask them nicely, right?
But first, I am NOT a raccoon!
Don't make me say it again!
Seems like I got along okay with the baby bird at least.
Should be no problem.
I hope.
Hey, raccoon.
Me not want to say me no trust you, but me not thinking mean bird's gonna listen so well
to nicely asking.
When bird get angry, then we go do attacking.
You!
Listen up!
I have a really important favor to ask of you.
The humans in the forest have a problem, and a bunch of them could die without your help!
Huh?
You say you're not letting them take the treasure?
And what treasure is that?
Bird angry!
Something else is dead!
Ow!
Rubble!
Arm point!
What treasure are you protecting?
Why do you hate humans?
Why do you want them to suffer?
You're here!
Talk no good against mean bird!
One choice left.
No one else.
The universe ends...
everyone ess Tumbies
and people do not fail, aren't they?
No!
They're scared and they love to be funny.
Oh, man! I can't get the humans or the birds on this stupid island to listen to a single word I'm saying!
The sun!
It's you! The chick from the other day! You sure grew up fast, didn't you?
Alright, listen up this time!
I get it now!
What happened? Raccoon make friends with birds after all?
Here's the deal! Turns out the birds have a good reason to act this way! They like to collect sparkly stuff, so they gathered treasure from all over the world and stored it on their home island! But when some bad guy humans found out about it, they came to their nest to steal their stuff and chase them away!
They were scared that the same thing might happen here, so they were just protecting themselves!
This plant! Use for medicine!
Guess that ought to do it!
I'm glad this worked out, because I'm going to need some more of that ointment as soon as you've got it!
Uh-oh! Raccoon's sleepy!
Huh!
It doesn't hurt!
Shiny! You can keep!
you can keep.
You guys already hit it off, huh?
Hey, a noose kill!
Thanks for the newspaper, buddy!
Let me see.
Meanwhile, on the sky island of Wetheria...
You're supposed to put your back into farm work, you know.
Goodness, you're such a lazy young lady.
I'm not lazy, you old sack of wrinkles!
I wanted to learn about weather,
not do manual labor in your stupid field while you lecture me!
I'm getting sick of this!
There's no reason you can't do both at the same time.
This isn't ordinary farming.
This weather field is where we grow all of our weatherballs.
Hard labor is essential to any scientific discovery, my dear.
Okay, you could have told me that before.
Well, well, it's a news cue of today's paper.
Why, thank you kindly.
My, what's all this nonsense about pirates?
What? Let me see that.
On the Grand Line's Bowen Islands...
Usopp has been rapidly gaining weight
by eating everything he can get his hands on.
How do you like these muscles?
The bounty of the forest is delicious,
but you must stop, Usoppin'.
Also, that's not muscle.
It's nothing but flab!
What if you get diabetes-ing?
Who cares? I'm strong now!
I tried to warn you.
Newspaper and...
Oh, yeah!
Chicken!
You're completely out of control!
On Peachy Island, in the Kamabaka Kingdom.
Oh, stop it, you.
Look at that gorgeous sunset.
Hey there, Mr. Bird.
Thank you, sugar.
Now, how's my horoscope today?
Check mine, too!
What the hell is this?!
At Tequila Wolf, in the East Blue...
Here, Nico Robin, take this.
Thanks for your help, but mind if I ask how you know my name?
Huh.
Every soldier in the Revolutionary Army knows who you are.
Now, if you'd be so 50 I'd be so close enough,
Without any further ado,
Now, if you'd be so kind,
I would like you to come along with us.
A kind offer.
But it's imperative that I see all of my friends again soon.
I see. That's a shame.
Ah, when you say your friends,
are you referring to the Straw Hat Pirates?
Because we happen to have a bit of information about them
that might be of interest to you.
What?
I thought that might get a reaction. Shall I tell you now?
Oh, yes, please do.
Anything at all would mean the world to me.
On the mechanical island of Future Land, Baltimore.
Finally!
Whoo!
Cola sure does go down smooth.
I miss the way it makes everything tingle.
I gotta say, I wasn't expecting to see a mechanical animal
inside the laboratory, though.
It was a polar bear.
It was a jerk!
But it punched me straight into a fridge
that was full of cola.
And then I torched him.
So I'd say everything's pretty cool.
Huh? What the heck?
On the Lazy Bones Island, Hungaria...
That's the most terrifying lamentation I've ever heard.
That howling can only mean that Lord Satan is summoning his demonic legions
to place an unspeakable curse upon the entire Long-Arm tribe.
Oh!
Turret, I just lost my train of thought.
Oh, my God!
That sounded like it came straight from the pits of hell.
45 degrees slant!
Wait, no! Should it be 60?
Oh!
How could I fall into such an awful slump?
Is this my punishment for all those panties?
Oh, my.
Save your strength, Roronoa Zoro.
Your wounds are too severe to ignore any longer.
And to be quite frank, you have no hope of defeating me if you lost to those apes.
Yeah, well, what the hell are you doing here?
I've been living in that castle for a while now.
What brings you here?
That would be one of your seven warlords, pals.
Kuma sent the whole crew flying.
I see.
That explains things, then.
Straw Hat was fighting with a different group in Marineford.
Hold on, did you see Luffy?
Is he all right?
What was he doing?
He should still be alive.
But as he left the battle, he appeared to be severely traumatized.
Why's that?
Don't you know his brother is dead?
It can't be!
And you're certain that's true?
Oh, no!
No way!
Really?
How can this be happening?
I can't believe it.
Fire Fist Ace died.
Right before Straw Hat's eyes.
Oh!
Luffy!
Determined to return to Sabaody and keep his promise to his crew, Luffy prepares for departure.
However, when Dark King Rayleigh appears and makes him a surprising offer, Luffy is forced to make a decision that could alter the fate of his entire journey on the Grand Line.
On the next One Piece, reunited with Dark King Rayleigh, decision time for Luffy, I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!